<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Bully Plub</string>
    <string name="hello_world">RelativeLayout</string>
    <string name="menu_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="piece_text"> </string>
    <string name="on">o</string>
    <string name="off"></string>
    <string name="tittle_num_pegs">Pegs:</string>
    <string name="newgamestr">Quick Game</string>
    <string name="aboutstr">About</string>
    <string name="paintstr">Paint</string>
    <string name="european_str">European</string>
    <string name="english_str">English</string>
    <string name="site_intial_str">Help</string>
        <string name="stats_intial_str">Statistics</string>
    
    <string name="about_text">
 
    		Bully Plub is a board game for one player involving
    		movement of pegs on a board with holes. Some sets use
    		marbles in a board with indentations. The game is known
    		simply as Solitaire in the United Kingdom where the card
    		games are called Patience. It is also referred to as
    		Brainvita (especially in India). According to a popular
    		story, the game was invented by a French aristocrat in the
    		17th century, when incarcerated in the Bastille, explaining
    		the games less common name Solo Noble. John D. Beasley ,author of The Ins and Outs of Bully Plub, has extensively
    		searched for evidence to support this, and has found it
    		lacking. The first reference to this story appeared in 1810,
    		more than a hundred years after the alleged event. He
    		believes that the colorful tale is fiction, yet it persists.
    		In other sources, the invention of the game is attributed to
    		the Native Americans—there is also no evidence to support
    		this. The first evidence of the game can be traced back to
    		the court of Louis XIV, and the specific date of 1697, with
    		an engraving made that year by Claude Auguste Berey of Anne
    		de Rohan-Chabot, Princess of Soubise, with the puzzle by her
    		side. Several works of art from that time show Bully Plub
    		boards, demonstrating that the game was highly fashionable.
    		The standard game fills the entire board with pegs except
    		for the central hole. The objective is, making valid moves,
    		to empty the entire board except for a solitary peg in the
    		central hole.
    	</string>
    <string name="camerastr">Profile Pic</string>
    
   
    <string-array name="type_board">
        <item>European(37 Pegs)</item>
        <item>English (33 Pegs)</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="type_board_codes">
        <item>37</item>
        <item>33</item>
    </string-array>
        
    
    <string-array name="figure_pref">
        <item>Normal</item>
        <item>Diamond</item>
        <item>Special</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="figure_pref_codes">
        <item>basic</item>
        <item>diamond</item>
        <item>special</item>
    </string-array>
    
    <string name="username">Username</string>
        <string name="npieces">Pieces</string>
        <string name="duration">Duration</string>
        

</resources>